[{"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 32, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 31}, {"answer": "I think so.", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 34, "question": "You've overtaken him?", "qSentId": 33}, {"answer": "A little bit.", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 36, "question": "Do you feel uncomfortable about that?", "qSentId": 35}, {"answer": "I mean, it's -", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 42, "question": "Is it?", "qSentId": 41}, {"answer": "I would absolutely say that marketing is a skill.", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 63, "question": "If you were to come on and I was to ask you, honestly, what is your talent, would you -- would you have any?", "qSentId": 62}, {"answer": "It doesn't hurt me.", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 75, "question": "-- we're laughing all the way to the bank?", "qSentId": 74}, {"answer": "It changes.", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 82, "question": "Yes, what do you put on your passport?", "qSentId": 81}, {"answer": "Something that I don't do.", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 85, "question": "Teacher?", "qSentId": 84}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 98, "question": "Do you think you are normal underneath all this gloss?", "qSentId": 97}, {"answer": "Everything.", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 110, "question": "You're liable for the petrol and the gas and the insurance, everything, right?", "qSentId": 109}, {"answer": "OURTNEY KARDASHIAN: That's a good question.", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 123, "question": "If you were to sum up your brand in one word, what would it be?", "qSentId": 122}, {"answer": "Everything they ask us -- because I think I'm -- I know -- and my sisters were heavily involved in our blogs and our Twitter and our Facebooks.", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 128, "question": "Brand for the fans?", "qSentId": 127}, {"answer": "Not at all.", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 163, "question": "You're not stupid, are you?", "qSentId": 162}, {"answer": "I think a lot of it is.", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 165, "question": "How much of your brand is based around body image?", "qSentId": 164}, {"answer": "I am, but I'm five feet tall.", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 178, "question": "Are you?", "qSentId": 177}, {"answer": "OK.", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 203, "question": "Are these life-sized?", "qSentId": 202}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 206, "question": "We're going to find out, aren't we?", "qSentId": 205}, {"answer": "Actually, you're -- yes, your one's taller than you.", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 212, "question": "Who's taller?", "qSentId": 211}, {"answer": "What do you like and don't like about your own --", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 218, "question": "Like, what do I like and don't like?", "qSentId": 217}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 231, "question": "I mean, is that -- do you see that as a plus?", "qSentId": 230}, {"answer": "I hated it, yes.", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 233, "question": "Kim, when you were young, you hated that, right?", "qSentId": 232}, {"answer": "They are real.", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 240, "question": "Are they real?", "qSentId": 239}, {"answer": "They're completely, 100 percent real.", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 242, "question": "Completely, 100 percent real?", "qSentId": 241}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 245, "question": "They're fake?", "qSentId": 244}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 249, "question": "You've had -- you've had surgery?", "qSentId": 248}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 251, "question": "And you haven't?", "qSentId": 250}, {"answer": "You have like I have an ugly day, when you look in the mirror and you're, like, oh, my God.", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 270, "question": "You know?", "qSentId": 269}, {"answer": "When I -- when I'm a little heavier because my body is petite, I see -- go to, you know, my thighs or something.", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 274, "question": "What is the part of you that you sometimes say, I wish that was better?", "qSentId": 273}, {"answer": "Obviously in the counterclockwise bed swirl, Kim.", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 326, "question": "What are you guys doing?", "qSentId": 325}, {"answer": "Well, we --", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 332, "question": "I mean, you're -- what is taking New York mean?", "qSentId": 331}, {"answer": "We are taking it to a Kardashian level, which basically means that --", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 334, "question": "Where are you taking it?", "qSentId": 333}, {"answer": "We're just opening up a clothing store, which is our store, Dash, that we -- we started one in L.A. And Kourtney and Khloe took Miami to open one up there.", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 337, "question": "What's that?", "qSentId": 336}, {"answer": "Because I'm the oldest and the best.", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 340, "question": "(INAUDIBLE), why are you first on the title?", "qSentId": 339}, {"answer": "It does.", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 347, "question": "Doesn't that make her the biggest star?", "qSentId": 346}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 349, "question": "Does that annoy you?", "qSentId": 348}, {"answer": "Kourtney could care -- I always say to everyone, Kourtney could care less about fame, about anything.", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 352, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 351}, {"answer": "No, the whole thing is extraordinary.", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 377, "question": "That she pulled the baby out herself?", "qSentId": 376}, {"answer": "Well, that -- well, that's why I didn't want the cameras there.", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 383, "question": "Do you expect any privacy?", "qSentId": 382}, {"answer": "Right.", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 392, "question": "Where was all the screaming and the yelling?", "qSentId": 391}, {"answer": "I don't know if I've a right.", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 396, "question": "Do you ever feel, you know, that you have any right to complain about paparazzi or intrusion into your private life once you've done that?", "qSentId": 395}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 408, "question": "Is anything off limits in your life, given you've put it all out there?", "qSentId": 407}, {"answer": "Exactly.", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 412, "question": "I'm assuming you've saved that to tell me all about it, haven't you?", "qSentId": 411}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 417, "question": "Did you know that?", "qSentId": 416}, {"answer": "A little.", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 423, "question": "I know you are, a big fan, right?", "qSentId": 422}, {"answer": "Ryan is so easy to talk to.", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 444, "question": "I mean, is he as evil to work with as I would hope he would be?", "qSentId": 443}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 451, "question": "Any bad points?", "qSentId": 450}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 466, "question": "Is there anything you wouldn't do for the cameras?", "qSentId": 465}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 470, "question": "I mean, would you -- would you record your own death?", "qSentId": 469}, {"answer": "Absolutely not.", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 473, "question": "Would you?", "qSentId": 472}, {"answer": "There's a lot that we wouldn't show.", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 481, "question": "Why not?", "qSentId": 480}, {"answer": "Like, I know in our New York season, I didn't feel comfortable having my son on the show.", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 487, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 486}, {"answer": "I would never move in with anyone unless I was engaged or married.", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 521, "question": "Is that true?", "qSentId": 520}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 524, "question": "Have I stumbled upon a bigger scoop?", "qSentId": 523}, {"answer": "No, I'm not.", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 526, "question": "You're not engaged?", "qSentId": 525}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 528, "question": "So, you're not moving in with him?", "qSentId": 527}, {"answer": "Well, Scott has his -- our place here, so --", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 533, "question": "You, just together?", "qSentId": 532}, {"answer": "I think that the way that I am -- I'm such a hopeless romantic --", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 540, "question": "Can you trust men, given what's happened to you?", "qSentId": 539}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 572, "question": "They'd have to believe in God?", "qSentId": 571}, {"answer": "I like tall, even though I'm five feet tall.", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 575, "question": "Dark?", "qSentId": 574}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 588, "question": "They're all these beefcakes, aren't they?", "qSentId": 587}, {"answer": "Six-foot-nine.", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 590, "question": "So how tall is your current guy?", "qSentId": 589}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 592, "question": "Is he really?", "qSentId": 591}, {"answer": "Five-foot-three.", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 595, "question": "And how tall are you?", "qSentId": 594}, {"answer": "Oh, it's the best way to feel skinny.", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 600, "question": "Be like a little Chihuahua if he takes you for a walk, isn't it?", "qSentId": 599}, {"answer": "Tiny and skinny.", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 602, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 601}, {"answer": "I'm happy.", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 610, "question": "Are you happy that Kim is now happy?", "qSentId": 609}, {"answer": "A little.", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 613, "question": "ORGAN: Do you feel protective, like a little big sister?", "qSentId": 612}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 624, "question": "Is he behaving himself now?", "qSentId": 623}, {"answer": "Love Johnny Depp.", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 634, "question": "Who do you think are the real hunks out there?", "qSentId": 633}, {"answer": "One day, I hope to get married, yes.", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 653, "question": "So are you going to get married?", "qSentId": 652}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 655, "question": "Sooner rather than later, do you think?", "qSentId": 654}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 674, "question": "What about for you?", "qSentId": 673}, {"answer": "I do, but I just think --", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 678, "question": "So you want to give your little one a happily married setup?", "qSentId": 677}, {"answer": "I have no idea.", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 687, "question": "-- and proposed, would you say \"yes\"?", "qSentId": 686}, {"answer": "I was on \"Dancing with the Stars\", and my partner was Mark Ballas, who was Bristol's partner.", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 714, "question": "What would you say if I said \"Sarah Palin\"?", "qSentId": 713}, {"answer": "You know, I know she gets a lot of flack, so I -- I don't know, I just tend to -- I don't typically like to say anything if I don't really have an opinion either way, to be honest.", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 719, "question": "Do you think that she's a good thing for America as a politician?", "qSentId": 718}, {"answer": "I think he's doing a good job.", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 722, "question": "Is he doing a good job?", "qSentId": 721}, {"answer": "He was definitely the strict parent when it was, you know, him and my mom.", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 727, "question": "What kind of man was he?", "qSentId": 726}, {"answer": "We were --", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 740, "question": "What kind of impact did that have on you two, do you think, looking back?", "qSentId": 739}, {"answer": "I think he would have been extremely proud of us.", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 761, "question": "What would your dad have made, do you think, of the success you've made of yourselves?", "qSentId": 760}, {"answer": "I think we did a really good job at telling him exactly how we felt, especially right before he passed away.", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 774, "question": "If you got the chance to talk to him again, what would you say that, perhaps, you never got to say when he was alive?", "qSentId": 773}, {"answer": "I just did.", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 790, "question": "Who says that?", "qSentId": 789}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 792, "question": "Yes, or no?", "qSentId": 791}, {"answer": "Combined, I would say, I don't talk dollars.", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 798, "question": "What, do you want to talk yen or pounds or Chilean pesos?", "qSentId": 797}, {"answer": "Kim is.", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 806, "question": "Are you?", "qSentId": 805}, {"answer": "I don't think it's ever appropriate to talk money.", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 812, "question": "Where are we going, here, 10, 30, 60, 80?", "qSentId": 811}, {"answer": "Every year.", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 821, "question": "Do you really?", "qSentId": 820}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 824, "question": "Ten percent of all your money?", "qSentId": 823}, {"answer": "I'm going to now.", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 827, "question": "Do you do that?", "qSentId": 826}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 834, "question": "So you've given away millions, then?", "qSentId": 833}, {"answer": "There's a charity that I work with a lot that I donate money all the time.", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 837, "question": "Which church do you give it to?", "qSentId": 836}, {"answer": "The Dream Foundation.", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 839, "question": "Do you want to name it?", "qSentId": 838}, {"answer": "And we have -- my mom has helped create a church.", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 842, "question": "So you've given them millions?", "qSentId": 841}, {"answer": "I think that it definitely -- when people say -- I mean, I get the statement when they say \"more money, more problems\" -- I definitely get that.", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 847, "question": "I mean, do you like being really rich?", "qSentId": 846}, {"answer": "We all try and make --", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 855, "question": "Who's the most generous?", "qSentId": 854}, {"answer": "Kourtney.", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 863, "question": "Who's the one who always says \"oh no, I've left my purse behind\"?", "qSentId": 862}, {"answer": "Yes, she is.", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 867, "question": "Kourtney is becoming a bit of a problem here financially, I think, isn't she?", "qSentId": 866}, {"answer": "No, it's fun, but I love to also --", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 870, "question": "You do?", "qSentId": 869}, {"answer": "Kim does it daily for herself.", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 877, "question": "What's the most extravagant thing either of you has ever bought for yourselves?", "qSentId": 876}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 882, "question": "OURTNEY KARDASHIAN: A watch for yourself?", "qSentId": 881}, {"answer": "115.", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 885, "question": "How much would that be?", "qSentId": 884}, {"answer": "Thousand.", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 887, "question": "115?", "qSentId": 886}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 889, "question": "Dollars?", "qSentId": 888}, {"answer": "Yes, but I got a really good deal on it.", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 891, "question": "One hundred fifteen thousand dollars for a watch?", "qSentId": 890}, {"answer": "I don't do that stuff for myself.", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 897, "question": "Did you ever imagine you'd be in a position to spend 115 thousand dollars on a watch?", "qSentId": 896}, {"answer": "Well, I don't have as much money as Kim.", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 901, "question": "Or you haven't got as much money as Kim?", "qSentId": 900}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 908, "question": "You do this with your mum, right?", "qSentId": 907}, {"answer": "Sometimes.", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 916, "question": "Ladies, do you ever fear over-exposure?", "qSentId": 915}, {"answer": "I would say so.", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 928, "question": "You know, and in your own way, you're living the American dream, aren't you?", "qSentId": 927}, {"answer": "I love women like Elizabeth Taylor and Sofia Loren and Ava Gardner.", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 934, "question": "Who do you idolize?", "qSentId": 933}, {"answer": "-- if he just married Liz Taylor.", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 944, "question": "He did?", "qSentId": 943}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 946, "question": "It would have made life so much easier, wouldn't it?", "qSentId": 945}, {"answer": "I would say, having my son.", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 963, "question": "The moment, if you got the chance, you'd relive again?", "qSentId": 962}, {"answer": "I would say, it was probably something that I didn't realize at the time, like a family ski trip with my dad and my mom.", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 966, "question": "What about you?", "qSentId": 965}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 973, "question": "That would be a special thing, wouldn't it?", "qSentId": 972}, {"answer": "They are some of the most finest Italian designs in the world.", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 995, "question": "Do you design them?", "qSentId": 994}, {"answer": "I've seen one outfit, and it looks pretty snazzy.", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 999, "question": "Have I got it in me?", "qSentId": 998}, {"answer": "A plus.", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 1003, "question": "Do you think the whole British thing might work?", "qSentId": 1002}, {"answer": "I'm beginning to think you may be the perfect person.", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 1006, "question": "Do you have a stylist?", "qSentId": 1005}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 1008, "question": "You want to style me?", "qSentId": 1007}, {"answer": "We all stammer, actually, It's bizarre how contagious a stammer is.", "docId": "110127pmt", "aSentId": 1026, "question": "Do you start stammering because you got so used to that voice?", "qSentId": 1025}]